Have you not thought about the consequences Osman?
Visit turkision.com for more!
If anything happened to my daughter...
...then I'd have to
kill your whole family, Osman!
They already killed my son, Yakup Bey!
Murderers!
Blood can only be washed with blood!
I will turn Kayi tribe into a bloodbath!
Ibrahim Bey
You are acting impulsively.
You speak impulsively.
I won't let brothers kill brothers in this tribe.
This will end terribly.
For us...
...there is no good ending anymore, Osman Bey!
Don't strike to kill, alps!
There are consequences to every move!
Come on!
Alps, take him!
Lots of blood will be spilled, my shahzade.
May Allah save us from
spilling our brothers' blood.
Alps! take him!
Stop!
Take them! Come on!
Alps!
Ibrahim Bey.
I understand your pain.
What you are going through is tough.
I realise it, but...
Still, this is my last warning.
Kill me here, Osman Bey.
Or I am going to fall upon you
like a calamity.
Melike Hatun! Calm down!
Calm down.
Your son killed my son, Bala!
You can't find his murderer by slanders.
Alaeddin wouldn't do that.
-The one who...
-You ordered it!
You did this!
You are the murderers!
This wedding was a trap set up for us!
You lured my son into a trap!
Watch your mouth, or I will break it!
I understand your pain.
But you are talking about my son here!
Murderers!
You'll pay for the blood you've spilled.
You smell blood. Blood!
You can't go anywhere.
Who are you, you dog?
What are you talking about?
I'm saying that...
You killed Ahmet.
Did you think you you could get away?
Ahmet?
Ahmet was alive when we left the tribe.
We didn't hurt anyone.
You're lying.
If you did something...
...be brave and own it.
You have Ahmet's blood on you.
We didn't kill anyone. Stand back.
Stand back?
No.
I'm here to rip off your hearts with my claws.
Only Allah knows if you can.
We'll see.
Find a good match for you Tugay.
You're no match for me Orhan Bey.
Come here.
I'm the one who'll
teach you now.
Only think you'll do is die.
Alps!
This is my tribe.
You won't spill kin blood here.
Why are you trying to stop the war...
...that you started Osman Bey?
It's in vain.
If I had started a war...
...you'd be defeated by now.
You took my daughter from me.
Now you're standing against me.
You..
..and your disgrace of a son...
...will pay for this.
We won't pay for anything.
Because there is no wrong here.
You don't have to fear for now Tugay.
But...
...just for now.
Alps!
Take him.
Tugay.
You're no match for me.
And you're no match for me Orhan Bey
You should have died long ago Cerkutay.
You think so?
Don't try anything Mehmet Bey.
Alps!
Ibrahim Bey
Your Alps have been stopped.
Calm down now.
Calm down.
There are two paths ahead of us.
Either you'll remain calm and trust justice...
...or...
...you'll act rashly...
...and you will act...
...with anger and die here.
After you shed all that blood...
...and acted so disrespectfully...
...which path will you...
...choose Osman Bey?
The arrow...
...is now out of the bow now.
The arrow will find it’s way to justice.
Justice will be served.
Don't worry.
But you...
You will act right too.
This is my last warning to you.
The last one.
Take them down.
Hold on. Don't get separated.
We're going this way, come on.
Hold on my Shahzade.
Didn't you say that they didn't
leave even one man standing behind?
Find me that archer. We're
going after them come on.
Praise be.
Come on.
Only Boran Bey can shoot that
fast. He's watching our backs.
We left our horses back there.
We have to lose them, come on.
Come on, hurry. Come on.
They won't make it out of here alive.
Find them for me.
This is the smell of fear.
We're going to find them by that.
Who are you?
You can't run now.
Ulucay's orders. Surrender.
Move now.
I only take orders from my bey
You scums.
Let him go.
Let him go. Don't touch him. Let go.
Don't touch him. Move.
Let him go.
Don't touch him.
Move back.
Let him go. Move.
No one will touch him. Move back.
Ahmet...
Son..
My son.
My son! I am here!
I am here.
son.
My child.
Even if it's not now...
...you will pay for it eventually, Bala Hatun.
Our children, Melike Hatun.
I lost mine too.
My Halime.
I buried her before I could embrace her.
Children
You will lose more of your children, Bala.
More!
Ahmet.
Son...
A mistake...
...is only forgiven once, alps!
Keep that in mind.
We don't want to kill you.
Don't force us to do that.
None of your alps died, alhamdulillah.
And the injured ones are being treated.
But this move did not suit you, Beys..
We don't always do what suits us, Gunduz Bey!
You are holding a wedding for your daughter!
I am holding a funeral for my son!
We brought shame to our ancestors who...
...spilled these lands to grow them!
If we had answered you' the same way today...
...blood of brothers would have been spilled.
But...
I won't allow that.
You say that you won't allow it...
...but what will
you do when it's...
....proven that it's your son Alaeddin that...
...killed my son, are you
going to execute him or not?
Or not!?
Will your justice be applied to your son!?
We are the followers of the prophet that did not...
...stay back from punishing his daughter Fatma!
Your doubt is an insult to us.
We will see, Osman Bey.
What will you see, Yakup Bey?
He is talking about the account they will give.
The account they will give.
What are we going to give
you an account for, Osman Bey?
How dare you say that!?
Look...
...you are in pain.
I know that.
That's why I am staying silent.
But when the time comes, you will..
...give an account for the alliance you made...
...against us, and the market that was attacked!
Do you have any proof to accuse us?
You are putting the blame on us
to stand on equal grounds with us!
I am not buying that, Osman Bey!
What are you talking about, Yakup Beyl?
Do you have any proof that my
son Alaeddin committed the murder?
Show me if you have!
No need to talk more.
...the killer of your son...
...is my son Alaeddin...
...you're free to kill...
...my son, Ibrahim Bey.
If my son...
..kidnapped your daughter...
...against her will, you're free
to kill Alaeddin, Yakup Bey.
Come on faster!
Come on!
We'll go there.
Alaeddin wait. We'll use that path.
This is our hunting area.
We have traps for animals. They can slow them down.
Come on! Come on!
People with Alaeddin are witnesses.
If they speak...
...it will be revealed he didn't kill Ahmet.
We'll kill them all.
They will all die.
Yakup Bey’s daughter too?
-She'll die.
There can be no witnesses.
All of them.
Gonca...
...and the rest.
Alaeddin!
You can't escape death.
You can't escape Ulucay.
Over here.
I will find my son.
There will be a court and justice will be served.
We'll fix this in peace...
..with no blood.
No.
I want blood for blood Osman Bey
...my son Alaeddin is guilty...
.then you'll get blood for blood...
You can't rule the court.
You support your son, OSman Bey.
Your justice can't be trusted.
How can we know that you won't protect...
...your murderer son?
What are you saying?
What?
What do you want?
Karesi...
...has a great Ulema...
Judge Rukneddin will come.
He'll rule the court..
We side by what's right.
Tell me Ibrahim Bey.
Do you want this?
This court..
...is for Ahmet's murder.
But..
...if something happened to Gonca...
..then...
..I won't wait for court.
-Cerkutay.
-My Bey.
Send word to the Karesi.
Invite Judge Rukneddin.
He'll rule the court.
As you wish my Bey.
But...
...we are true warriors.
If you call my son a murderer
before the court takes place...
...you're going to die.
You won't even be able to see the court.
Do you really trust your son this much?
I can kill you here.
But...
...I know Alaeddin wouldn't hurt your son.
I know...
...Ahmet wouldn't hurt anyone.
But I will hurt.
I'll kill a lot of men Osman Bey.
If you make a move before the court...
...your heads will drop first.
I swear...
...that I'm going to kill those...
...who did this to you.
That Alaeddin...
Stop there.
Melike Hatun.
Hold on.
You continue your slander
without knowing the truth.
Don't.
The truth?
You talk about the truth.
Come.
Come and see.
The truth is here come and look.
The truth is laying here ice cold.
You’re a mother.
I thought I would understand you the best.
But you continue to nurse your grudge.
We're going to find your son's killer despite you.
That's when you'll feel ashamed.
We know the killer. It's your son.
Alaeddin. Alaeddin did this.
He kidnapped my son's fiance.
He disrespected his honor.
He took my son's life, what are you talking about?
Your anger is blinding your mind.
Feel your pain with honor.
Am I to learn about honor from you Bala?
Am I to learn it from you?
-Melike Hatun.
-Bala.
Am I to learn it from you?
-Let me go.
-Melike Hatun.
Let me go.
Come to your senses Melike
Hatun. What are you doing?
Let me go.
Don't test me. I'm at my limit.
Bala, this is nothing.
I'm going to end your bloodline Bala.
Just wait Bala.
You're going to meet Melike Hatun now.
Bala.
Look here, I'm forgiving you this time.
But if you repeat it even your
pain won't be enough to save you.
Elcim.
Girl, when she says goodbye to her son....
...let the Baciyans keep watch.
-Okay Bala Hatun.
-Let me go.
We will do as you say.
Get out!
We chose the wrong thing Gonca.
We should've taken the other way around.
Alaeddin.
This is our hunting grounds.
There are traps everywhere.
Look.
So you say we're going to
draw them to the traps huh?
That's right.
They're coming closer. Step where I step.
-Come on.
Be careful.
They're changing directions.
They're going deeper into the forest.
But they still have the. smell of fear on them.
I'm going to find them by it.
Come on.
Stop.
They're there. Come on.
Stop
I said stop.
Stop.
My shahzade.
My shahzade!
The traps worked.
It will keep them busy.
Thank Allah, good.
But it won't stop them. We need to run.
Come on.
Goodness gracious!
They are like rabid dogs!
It's just a scratch, it's okay.
Come on.
Keep your eyes on her.
Melike Hatun will not stay put.
Her disrespect shouldn't go unpunished, Bala Hatun.
It won't, my father will punish
her when he hears about it.
No, my girl.
Your father will not know.
Things are in a chaos, he
will get angrier. Don't tell him.
Do you want her to get away with it?
She tried to hurt you, she spilled your blood.
Don't worry Bala Hatun.
We won't tell anything to anyone.
But...
...Alaeddin Bey...
...how is he going to clean his name?
My shahzade wouldn't do anything like that.
He wouldn't, but...
...what if he had to kill Ahmet Bey?
That's what I am scared of.
What if he was trying to protect himself?
Or Gonca?
We will learn when we find Alaeddin.
It's not as we think.
Mother, mother.
What if my brother is guilty?
Mother, what will happen to my brother?
Ibrahim Bey wants to kill him.
That means war.
May Allah protect.
Brothers would kill each other!
No my girl. Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid.
Your father wouldn't let a war...
...to break out, or brothers to kill each other.
Don't be afraid.
I hope so.
They martyred my brave son treacherously!
I can't wait for their justice, Yakup Bey!
We won't wait, Ibrahim Bey.
Before Osman destroys the evidence...
..we will get him!
My Bey.
The wounded alps are treated.
The remaining alps are taken to the caged tent.
Osman...
He hides behind the lies of
justice, and wants to save his son.
But he won't do it.
He thinks he has the upper hand.
He imprisoned the alps.
He keeps us under watch.
But we will strike him...
Alps are watching us.
Let's go to the tent.
We all know Shahzade Alaeddin.
He wouldn't do something like that.
There is something else going on.
My Bey, forgive me but...
...a man has only one weakness, his heart.
What if Ahmet Bey crossed the line?
Said something bad?
Is that what my son learned from me?
You all know well:
No, my son wouldn't do that.
We have fought many of our own
kin. We haven't killed any before.
My sons are educated with the virtues of the state.
They wouldn't do anything without
thinking of the consequences.
It's not about heroism. It's about the state.
you know who brought the trouble...
...then you should look at
who benefits from it. Tell me...
...who would benefit from
Turks fighting each other?
The crusaders my Bey.
Mongolians.
Yes. We'll reveal those who wish to trick us.
But the real issue...
...is the liar among us.
Ibrahim Bey.
He won't stop hurting us.
Yakup Bey's looking for a way to end us.
But we won't allow tricks.
We'll reveal the liars without
spilling brother's blood.
When I get my son's corpse...
right in front of me...
...I want Alaeddin's dead body too.
War will come of this.
The borders will be a hell hole.
Yakup Bey.
Eventually...
...this was going to happen.
Mehmet.
You'll kill Alaeddin.
Gonca?
...don't have a daughter named Gonca.
You know what to do.
When war breaks out...
...we'll be at the fore front.
You want to spill brother's blood.
What needs to happen will happen Tugay.
Tomorrow...
...Ahmet's funeral will be held.
It is a good day to fight...
...after a long time of quiet.
What's on your mind my Bey?
Yes.
Ulcay and Alps...
...will go to the cemetery...
..and save us from the cages.
Now...
Listen carefully.
Since Sultan Mesut died...
...we stopped war at all times.
We always made an effort for it.
We can't back down anymore.
So we'll fight.
We didn't start it.
But we'll see it end, if Allah permits.
If Allah permits. my Bey.
Gunduz Bey.
Send Alps to north of Candaroglus.
Will Alps shoot their arrows?
They shoot their arrows and swing their swords.
It is too late now.
Now tell your Alps the news.
As you wish.
It is your order Osman Bey.
The tribe..
...belongs to you and Solgur Aga.
As you wish my Bey.
Thank you.
Come on. We know where
Alaeddin and Gonca will meet.
Let's go to Alaeddin and find out the truth.
Come on. Come on Alps.
Here, my Shehzade.
The tribe's crowded.
We can't escape.
We'll use the training area.
Come.
As you wish my Shehzade.
Come on brave boys.
Show me how you use a sword.
Come on.
Praise be, praise be to our brave men.
We're close to the horses.
Come on.
Come on, with the name of Allah, Shahzade.
You showed us your master of sword fighting.
Let us see how good you
are with the bow too, come on..
Come on, get your bows.
Come on.
Fatma Hatun.
What if they get caught?
What if Gonca Hatun and the Tall Shahzade die?
Ghazi.
Say good things.
That won't happen.
My brother can take care of himself.
Watch it.
Don't worry about these.
Practice well, there is a fight in the horizon.
Stop.
What are you doing here?
Hold on.
We're getting our freedom.
Ghazi go and tell the alps,
someone is running away.
Okay.
Stop.
Where are you running off to?
Let me go.
Let go.
You're at the wrong place at
the wrong time, Fatma Hatun.
You won’t make it out of the tribe.
Fatma Hatun.
What are you doing?
Don't get close or I'll kill Fatma
Hatun without blinking an eye.
Make way.
Or I'll make it with Fatma Hatun's blood.
Come on.
Make way.
Who is going to save you once
Osman Bey hears about it, Mehmet Bey?
Even Osman Bey won't be able to save
you when Germiyan's army comes for you.
Come on.
Fitnat.
Once we're out of the tribe give them Fatma Hatun.
Come on.
Alps.
Follow them.
You snake.
What will we do now Shahzade?
First we're going to go to the market
and figure out where that Alaeddin went.
I'm going to...
...kill him and his lover with my bare hands.
Come on.
But first, we're going to lose Osman's dogs.
We're going to go into the
forest and lose them Kanyumaz.
Come on.
As you wish my Shahzade.
Let me go.
Let go.
Put her in the tent with the cage. Take her away.
Wait! I am going to make you pay!
Move!
Let go of me!
Inform Osman Bey that Mehmet escaped.
They wanted to...
...take justice in their own hands.
I hope they will be stopped
before anything happens.
I hope so.
We wanted this to > be resolved in a trial...
..but you schemed behind our backs!
I don't trust you!
We don't trust you either!
That's why we did it, Gunduz Bey!
If Mehmet does anything on his own...
...apart from your deal with Osman Bey...
...you will all pay for this!
We paid the price!
Take them!
Keep your eyes on them!
I don't want another mistake, Aykurt.
Okay my Bey.
What happened?
Mehmet Bey escaped, my Bey
What?
How could he?
He used Fatma Hatun and Gazi; and escaped.
Are they okay?
They are okay, thank Allah.
Oh Allah.
They used the children to escape, huh?
What were you doing?
How am I going to trust you
and leave things to your hands?
It won't happen again, my Bey.
If it happens...
...you know what your punishment will be.
I knew they wouldn't stay put.
What will we do now Osman?
Mehmet is going to go after Alaeddin.
We won’t stop either.
-Orhan.
-My Bey..
Go after Alaeddin.
You know where he is.
I will return with my brother,
or don't return at all, my Bey.
Don't worry.
We will go to the frontier market.
Let's learn what happened.
That's the only way to stop the war.
Hasan.
Now, go to Gunduz Bey.
Tell him...
...to keep his eyes on Ibrahim and Yakup Beys.
As you command my Bey.
Come on!
Caravansary.
What happened? You lost
your mind after getting punched?
Anything can happen to you in life.
Now you are my prisoner.
Well, those who look themselves in a...
giant's mirror will keep falling down.
What did you do with Konur? Has he not come at all?
He came.
I took care of him, and listened to his intentions.
His path is ghaza path...
...and his cause is the cause of the Haqq.
I am sure of it now.
Konur is my brother again
And our paths are the same..
You realized it now, huh?
Then tell me, where is Konur?
He went to Ibrahim Bey..
He will accept his offer then.
I don't know.
But shahzade Alaeddin..
...people say that he killed shahzade
Ahmet while kidnapping Gonca Hatun.
I don't believe it.
But everyone keeps speaking of this.
This means war Boran.
Oh no.
What did Ibrahim Bey do?
He was at my Bey's tribe.
I don't know the rest.
Konur went to Ibrahim Bey for this.
Konur owes Ibrahim Bey his life.
He'll pay his price and go on his own way.
Since we walk the same path...
...untie me and let's get to our business.
Okay.
Germiyanoglu Border - Frontier Market
Can't I rely on you, huh?
My sister was abducted!
And you didn't even hear a thing.
When this is done you'll be punished.
Stand back.
Kayyumaz.
-My Shehzade?
-Make them work at the hardest areas.
I want them dead tired.
As you wish Shehzade.
Any trace, Kayyumaz?
My Bey. Someone helped them get in.
We suspect Gulce Hatun.
People saw her.
Idiot!
Don't pity her when you find her.
Send a messenger to Kutahya and Kastamonu.
War has begun.
Send Alps to borders. Kayi
will be erased from earth.
As you wish my Shehzade.
Adra.
-Yes?
Go to Mekece Castle.
We'll give them a chance to take revenge on Osman.
Tell them what happened.
They'll ready their soldiers.
We'll need their support for the war.
I’ll do my best to involve them in the war.
Before Osman I'll find Alaeddin and Gonca.
They're still after us.
We couldn't escape.
If we could erase our track.
I'll find a way.
You'll go through there...
and I...
Alaeddin.
What do you mean?
We'll leave together.
No.
We can't escape together Gonca.
They'll find our tracks.
I'll make them follow me.
And you'll go to the cave.
I won't leave your side.
We'll go together.
Sweetheart.
Even if there's death?
No.
I won't lead you to death Gonca.
Know it.
Even if there's death Alaeddin.
But..
...if you insist...
...then find a way to live.
They want to poison our love...
...with tricks and evil plans.
Do you regret it Gonca?
We're together.
I have no regrets.
We'll get to the end together.
If it’s together...
...even death sounds nice Alaeddin.
Praise be!
You'll kill the enemies right Gonca?
Shehzade.
They found us. They're coming closer.
Come on Gonca. Come on.
Come on.
Come here.
Holofira.
You should go to the tribe.
No.
No, don't ask that from me
I won't leave you.
If my father knows he must have be on his way.
You might come across him
on your way, you can get us help.
Go now.
Holofira you did everything you could.
But we don't know what awaits, we can't
put your life in danger anymore. Go now.
Let Gulce go.
Holofira, we don't have time.
Go now.
Holofira Hatun.
Go.
Okay.
I promise you, I'm going to bring you that help.
May Allah help you on your way.
Come on.
Come on Gonca, Baysungur, Gulce. We're leaving.
Stand back Osman Bey, what are you doing here?
I won't warn you again Osman Bey.
Brothers.
Alps don't take mercy.
Brothers what are you doing?
My bey.
Brothers, it's me.
Cerkutay.
The Cerkutay who you shared your...
...food with, who you defeated the same enemy with.
Brother hear me out, did I ever lie to you?
No I wouldn't.
There is unrest among us.
It made us become enemies to each other.
Listen.
Listen to me, this is the
work of a two headed snake.
Osman Bey...
...is here to reveal this trap.
Brothers.
Lower your weapons.
Everything you heard were lies, alps.
Our son Alaeddin...
...didn't kill Shahzade Ahmet.
This truth will be revealed sooner or later.
Come on.
Make way, alps.
Make way so that..
...you live a long life.
Alps.
Know that we won't let any of you live.
Don't.
Look.
.We...
..don't want to spill our brothers' blood here.
You know that too.
Come on.
Make way.
Tell me.
Where did they kill Shahzade Ahmet?
The fight happened mostly inside.
No, it wouldn't take this long if it was Alaeddin.
It wouldn't.
But...
Look here.
They killed Ahmet here.
That poor kid died for no reason.
If Alaeddin had done it, he would
have killed Germiyan alps too.
My son did not do it.
Bala.
Osman.
He is our Alaeddin Ali.
He wouldn't do this.
What if...
...it was an accident?
What will we do then?
Justice is blind, Bala.
Allah is the One that gives
also the One that takes.
But...
...Alaeddin wouldn't kill his brother.
If he had done this...
then he will accept the punishment.
Come on.
These are the alps that were
on duty that night, my Bey.
Who else was there that night?
The merchants, and Ibrahim Beys private men.
Not his alps?
Who were they?
A bandit called Ulcay was leading.them.
He uses dual swords.
Dual swords, huh?
That's the jackal that saved konur.
What else?
When they saw that Ahmet Bey was
dead, they went after Alaeddin Bey.
My Bey.
We found Alaeddin Bey's horse outside the market.
They must be running on foot.
Come on, quickly!
We will go there quickly.
We won't rest until we find them, come on.
Ulcay!
Look at him.
Palace Bey is in the forest.
Be careful, or your boots
might get muddy, Mehmet Bey.
I know you are after Alaeddin.
Tell me, where is that pervert!?
They are not far away.
Your sister Gonca is together with Alaeddin.
They were running while holding each other's hands.
I am going to kill Alaeddin, Gonca....
...and that traitor Gulce!
That's what we both want.
Tell me first.
What's the situation of Ibrahim Bey?
Osman keeps my father and Ibrahim Bey prisoner.
You will free them.
Ahmet will be buried in Kayi graveyard tomorrow.
You will attack then and save my father.
That’s what they want.
Consider it done.
But first, we need to get rid of these dogs.
Go that way.
Come on!
Kanyumaz!
Come on Kanyumaz!
If Gonca..
....tell her brother Alaeddin didn't
kill Ahmet, things will fall apart.
Find them before the others.
As you wish Ulcay.
...Hatun speaks...
Mehmet will die.
As you wish Ulcay.
When Yakup Bey hears Beyhood wars will begin.
Ulcaytu Han wants this
Come on! Find them now!
Come on Alps.
They shot Alaeddin.
They went that way.
Come on Osman Bey. Hurry!
Come.
Holofira.
Osman Bey.
My girl.
Alaeddin Bey's in trouble.
Where are they?
They're trapped. They're being chased there.
Don't worry.
We'll make it in time.
Oguz.
-My Bey.
Take Holofira to the tribe.
As you wish my Bey.
Come on my girl.
We don't have time.
Let's go now.
Back on the horses.
Come on.
There.
They're too many.
We can't fight them.
Gonca.
We can't do it if we're together.
What do you mean?
I said what I said Alaeddin.
We'll stick together.
I know Gonca.
But we don't have another choice.
You and Gulce will go to the caves.
Wait there for us.
No. I won't leave you.
We'll come after you.
We won't resist.
We'll take their horses and come for you.
But if you move forward it'll be easier.
Me and Baysungur can fight them off and escape.
Right. Shehzade is right.
If it's less people...
...we'll be able to sneak.
Right?
They’re approaching.
Promise.
You'll come.
I promise. My sweet Gonca.
Don't you worry.
We'll be there before you get there.
I'll wait.
Okay.
Come on.
Gulce
Watch my back.
O Allah!
-Cerkutay!
-My bey
Check the tracks.
Allah, forsake our kids...
Don't worry at all Bala, we're going to find them.
My bey.
The tracks are very confusing.
They lead to everywhere.
I can't understand which way they went to.
Don't worry, we're going to separate too.
-Cerkutay.
-My Bey.
Go that way.
Bala you go this way.
I'll go this way.
We're going to find them, come on.
We will.
-Come on.
Alaeddin.
We should go Gonca Hatun.
Alaeddin Bey can take care of himself.
Alaeddin keeps his promises.
He'll come since he promised he will.
Come on
Gonca.
Don't run.
Run.
Come here. Come here Gonca.
Come here Gonca.
How much longer will you run for?
So you took my sister hostage
to run away from the tribe...
I'm going to end your bloodline.
Get up now.
First Alaeddin.
...then you. I'm
going to kill you both
I would've taken your life
right here right now but...
...you're not worth it Mehmet.
You're not worth it.
He's here...
..but his lover isn't.
Kill them both.
That woman is more important for us.
We have to find her. before Mehmet does. Come.
Shahzade, you should go. I can keep them busy..
No.
We,either die together or live together Baysungur.
Orhan Bey.
There's a fight going on that way.
Alps.
Tie him up.
He's coming with us to the
tribeCome on Elcim Hatun.
Brother.
Do you think you're alone?
Brother..
Come on alps! Leave none alive!
-Mother?
-Son!
I wouldn't leave you to their mercy!
Hold on! We still have lots to do!
-Mother!
-Son, are you okay?
I am okay mother.
-Come on, we are leaving.
-Come on.
Come on.
This way.
Come on!
They found us! Oh Allah, protect Alaeddin.
Where are you running to, woman?
This great forest., can’t hide you from us.
The skies want you to die today.
Capture them!
I will wash in your sacred blood today!
You will die suffering!
Leave Gonca alone!
You jackal!
You are the one that's going to die.
Osman.
Yeah, Osman!
Don’t interfere.
I am going to split your face in two now!
May the souls be my witness, I
won't be defeated by you Osman!
I got your whip now!
Come here!
Osman!
You shouldn't have let me taste blood!
Is that so? You will drown in your own blood.
Now tell me about the plan made against my son!
Who is behind it?
Who!?
Who killed Shahzade Ahmet!?
You will tell me all!
Do you understand? If you want
a quick death, you will tell me all.
Come here!
The skies don't want me to die today.
I will come again.
I will come again!
My shahzade!
Don't get close! Stay there!
Stay back, you dog!
My shahzade!
You don't look well, my shahzade.
Gonca!
We will find her.
But not now.
Come on, my shahzade.
Come on.
Gonca.
I'll find you Gonca.
Come on.
Gonca!
Are you okay?
I'm okay. But Alaeddin needs help.
Gonca?
Alaeddin.
Are you okay my girl?
I'm okay Bala Hatun.
Are you okay?
Ulcay attacked.
Osman Bey came right on time.
What's going on my Bey?
The jackals eat the lamb.
And shepherds grieve them.
But we'll find the jackal.
We'll find him.
Osman.
I will...
...kill both you and your son.
Today...
...I bury my son...
...but tomorrow...
...I will take the land I bury him from you.
It's your fault.
My son died because of you.
I told you Ibrahim.
I said this marriage won't be good for us.
How could I know Hatun?
How could I know...
...Osman would do such an evil thing...
...and dare to wrong the Turkmen?
We did the right thing.
But Osman..
-Osman!
Osman!
You keep saying Osman!
What are you doing Hatun?
It was a political move.
Damn your politics.
Ibrahim.
Damn your Beylic.
You're a bad father.
Melike Hatun!
Get it together.
Stop it.
Don't speak of my beylic.
My son...
...died for the future of our beylic.
Died.
Look. He's gone.
Ahmet's gone. He died.
Look.
Look at it.
This cloth..
...and this cold sword is all that's left.
Just look.
Ahmet's sword...
..is mine now.
All the blood I shed...
....will be to avenge him.
Promise me.
You will find the murderer who did this to Ahmet...
...and you won't let him live another day.
Promise me.
Hatun, your hand.
Your hand's bleeding.
No.
My heart...
My heart's bleeding.
I promise Melike.
I promise, my Hatun.
I'll avenge our son.
Alaeddin...
I'm not just going to kill them.
I'm going to do something so
much worse than death to them.
I'm going to make those who set
that precious heart of yours aflame...
...live hell on this earth.
I promise.
If you...
you go back on your word... If
...because of politics...
...then I won't forgive you.
I'll take their lifes...
...and yours.
Ahmet...
Son...
Alaeddin, tell me what happened at the market.
How did Ahmet die? Did you..
I am not involved, mother.
He was alive when we left the tribe.
So?
While I was freeing Gonca from the prison tent...
...Ahmet came in, my bey.
We fought but I didn't kill him.
He was knocked out when we left.
Alaeddin knocked out even
the alps, he didn't hurt anyone.
Then who killed Ahmet?
They want the Turks to kill each other.
The beys have to attack each
other for them to start the war.
That's why they killed Ahmet and framed you for it.
Who would want such a bloody war?
Either Mongols or the infidels.
Who else wants the Turks to fight?
What about Ulcay?
When did he start going after you?
They cut us off right after we left the tribe.
That means they followed you. When you left...
...they went in and killed Ahmet.
Looks like it's Ulcay who is holding the ropes.
My bey.
There is also Boran Bey.
He was watching our backs.
Then he retreated.
Boran is still trying to do things alone.
He's trying to protect us all by himself.
My bey, he can't leave you.
As you know, he has good intentions.
I know Cerkutay, of course I know.
But his punishment is decided.
What will we do now my bey?
Now
Everyone is tired right now.
It's going to get dark.
We're going to the caves.
We will spend the night there.
Why aren't we going to the tribe my bey?
You shouldn't be seen until the trial.
Now..
Yakup Bey and Ibrahim Bey.
They're quite angry. We
don't know what they might do.
I have good news.
Alaeddin Bey.
Daughter Gonca.
Tonight is very important for you.
Mother, what is it?
It's a good thing.
Tonight...
...an Imam will come to the cave.
You're going to get married.
What are you saying father?
Mother.
My amazing brother.
Brother.
You're getting your happy ending after all huh?
Thank Allah brother, thank Allah.
First, we need to have a good dinner, huh Beys?
Hunt somethings.
Come on, show us your skills.
Come on.
This is the place.
So he placed his camp on this jackal den, huh?
He is a jackal after all.
Look.
That's his Post.
His Post is there, but he is not here.
We will wait for him to come.
We should retreat now before he smells us.
Come on brother.
Move!
You are late.
Osman saved Alaeddin and
Gonca. Took them somewhere hidden.
It looks like they knew about it.
They kidnapped your sister,
when you went to the wedding.
Alaeddin will pay for this with his life!
Either him, or me! There is no
other way. I will cleanse this dishonor!
What are you going to do about
it? Your sister also wanted this.
My soldiers heard it. Your
sister went with him willingly
And your sister fought against us with them.
Gonca will get her punishment too.
I am going to give her
punishment with my own hands.
We know very well
about the great Germiyans' power
Is Kayi going to get away with this, Mehmet Bey?
Gather your army.
If this isn't the time to fight, then when is it?
The army will be ready. This
war will be the end of Kayis.
But first, we need to save them.
Don't worry.
I will save them from Osman.
You should go and gather your army.
I heard of you.
I trust you.
If it wasn't you I'd be worried.
You're right.
When my fathers are safe...
...the army must be ready.
Okay.
Okay, Mehmet Bey.
Come on.
Go fast.
Come on Kayyumaz.
Little jackals.
We're going back.
We'll tell Ilkhanid governor about this.
Then the great war begins.
We need Warriros.
Allah tells us...
...that evil plans are set soon.
When it comes...
those who sit..
...those who stand...
..and those who walk will share different fates.
Peace be with you.
Peace be upon you.
Allah speaks of a time as this.
Do you think it's close?
Are there ones who betray religion for the world...
...and lie with no end to gain power...
...and repeat the process over and over?
Are there ones who think
awful things about brothers?
Awful things, Dervish Efendi?
People kill their brothers.
If we didn't see it happen...
..it's called slander.
Allah forbid.
Tugay Alp.
So....
...we're in that time.
Evil's a strong presence.
Then we must go with sunnah.
Let me tell you about it.
To be away from evil...
the less we move..
the better we are.
Muslims can't stay put.
We move.
That's what we know Dervish.
That's why I am confused by your words now.
Can you see when it's foggy Tugay?
If you don't see with your eyes...
.but with the eyes in your heart...
...don't say it.
Evil break the eyes in our hearts.
Who's right or wrong...
...who's honorable and who's
weak can't be determined.
If you can't determine it...
...you must wait.
You must wait for evil to go..
...and the fog to be lifted.
And for the curtains to be lifted from the eyes.
If not...
...brothers fight each other...
...and infidels arise.
Great Allah says...
..."Muslims are brothers."
If Muslim brothers...
...don’t find those who are traitors...
...among them...
...the infidels...
...will reign with their cruelty.
That’s why...
...when the evil comes...
...we must see who works with the infidels...
..and who follows evil...
and betrays the brotherhood...
..to cause chaos.
Then...
...we must stand against it.
Salvation comes from only this.
Osman Bey.
My father and Ibrahim Bey.
They united with Mekece Tekfur for trade.
It scares me.
They're blinded.
To destroy you...
...they'll start the war.
Don't worry my girl.
You don't need to be scared,
we won't allow this war to happen.
The fight has started,
with bloodied swords too.
But the fight of love has been...
...won by love.
May our unity be everlasting if Allah permits.
If Allah permits.
If Allah permits. mother, if Allah permits.
Once we get this trail over...
We're going to have the celebration, right my bey?
We will.
We have lots to do.
If I knew we would
have celebrations like this...
...one after the other,
I would've prepared myself.
Don't worry Bala Hatun we will all work
together and get the dowry ready quickly.
It will be all ready before
Gonca comes to the tribe.
Come on.
Everyone is here but me, praise be!
I was feeling like I was missing something.
Now that you're here, I’m complete.
Come, my beautiful daughter.
We can't do without you daughter, come here.
I brought the imam brother.
You see my hard work right?
I know sister.
May Allah bless everyone
with a sister as caring as you.
Ameen.
Come on.
Why did you bring this smelly dog into my den?
For me to strangle?
We heard about what happened.
Ibrahim Bey is being kept as a captive by Osman.
Brother Boran is friends
with Konur, to work with you...
So...
...you are the one who was exiled with Konur.
Boran.
Where is Konur?
You saved Konur's life, I heard about it.
He went to Ibrahim Bey to help.
I didn't hear from him after that.
You smell Boran.
You smell like a skunk.
But you smell more like...
...betrayal.
If I wanted to betray yourself I
would've told your enemy your location.
If I did...
...neither you nor your men
would've been alive right now.
I like you Boran.
I like you.
I'm going to give my men that...
...smelly lands of Osman...
....his great palaces...
...and Kayi's red cheeked women.
You stay silent.
You don't say anything.
Are you still feeling...
...affection towards Osman?
If Osman finds me he would shred me to pieces.
Affection.
What affection?
I feel sick when hear his name.
Then I'll tell you what I'll do with Osman.
I am going to break his cycle!
I am going to skin him and his family...
...and make boots out of them!
I will wash in the blood of the alps!
You are underestimating Osman.
Be careful.
He might...
...skin you and your dogs...
...and make a tent out of them!
Would you like that to happen?
Or would you like to see Osman kneel before me?
See his tribes on fire?
See his women serving me?
I set on a path together with Konur.
is what the fate is going to show us.
And we will live and see it together.
Only I can determine your fate.
You will taste...
...the death from my hands.
In the name of Allah, the merciful, the beneficent.
I witness there is no god
other than the one Allah, and
I bear witness Mohammad
is his servant and messenger.
Yakup's daughter Gonca Hatun,
do you accept Osman Bey's son...
...shahzade Alaeddin as your
husband with the mehr of 500 gold coins?
I do.
Do you?
I do
Osman Bey's son Shahzade Alaeddin.
Do you accept Yakup Bey's daughter Gonca Hatun...
...as your wife for the mehr of
500 gold coins you promised?
I do.
Do you?
Do you witness this?
We do.
Do you?
May Allah accept it.
Oh sacred stones, speak!
Let the sky talk, let the earth listen!
Let this skunk's fate be decided!
Let blood be spilled!
The Tengri of the sky show us the way!
Let this skunk's fate be decided!
Tengri has spoken.
Stop, stop.
Stop!
Let me tell you what.
I will wpeak words that you haven't heard before.
Look.
Come on.
I am curious about what a mortal man...
..so close to death will say.
Listen Ulcay, I have words for you.
Why did you even come out in the battlefield?
Stay away from me don't come close.
You look like a dog wearing a jackal's fur.
Look at Osman's old servant.
He looks pathetic.
You're a weak man with a bad smell.
You'll only sleep in the land you wish to own.
If you wish to kill me now.
I can kill you right here right now.
I like you Boran.
I like you.
Prepare food for our guests.
We'll share our last food with them.
Boran..
Don't forget.
Your sword didn't save you.
Your qopuz did.
Allah.
Protect our children and wives.
Ameen.
Make us victorious against those who bring us down.
Allah bless you.
My Bey.
I hope so, my Bey.
May Allah keep you with us.
Thank you.
Mother.
I hope the best, son.
I hope so, mother.
-May Allah bless you.
-Thank you Osman Bey.
My brother.
After battles, you finally won at love.
Because I have a strong brother.
I know that you keep forgetting me.
Not without you Fatma.
Gonca, my girl.
Don't forget. From now on...
...you are my daughter too.
May Allah keep you two together.
Ameen.
I know, Bala Hatun.
Thank you.
It was a hard time for you.
I hope you'll stay together easily.
I hope so.
Thank you Elcim Hatun.
Daughter Gonca.
We had to do it like this now
but once everything's okay...
...we'll have a nice feast.
Don't worry okay?
You're our daughter.
We're like this because your
father made some mistakes.
If that wasn't the case we were going to
come and ask for your hand at your tribe.
I know Osman Bey.
I wish....
...my mother and father didn't
fell victim to their greed.
Wish they were with me.
But they aren't.
That's okay.
I'm sure of both...
...my path and my companion.
Feed yourself.
So?
Tell us Ulcay.
Are we going to let Osman keep Ibrahim Bey captive?
We're going to save them.
That’s what's keeping this war going.
Especially...
...when this finds it's way to likhanids...
...an army which will come from Konya...
...will set their great steps
on these foul smelling lands.
Then, Osman's beyhood will meet it's end.
Come on.
It’s time to feed.
I still can't believe it Alaeddin.
Our wedding which was held in the sky first...
...is finally real on earth too.
We got married.
We are one.
No one but death can do us apart now.
I always said it was going to be hard.
But even I didn't think it would be this hard.
My whole past, my mother...
my father...
I left them all behind.
I don’t regret it.
Don't get me wrong.
But there is a fire in my heart Alaeddin.
It burns so much...
Gonca...
...the fire in your heart...
...would turn me into ashes, my wife.
My wife.
I'll always be here.
With you.
I'll protect you like your father.
I'll love you with compassion like your mother.
Don't feel incomplete at all.
My doe eyed love.
And I will...
...love you...
...as much as my heart and strength allows me to.
I'll always be with you my husband.
Gonca...
My test started in a cave.
I learned that I'll never have a child ever again.
But in another cave...
...gave birth to my child.
And we held his wedding in another cave.
Then we will hold their wedding in the cave.
No, no way.
I am going to hold a legendary wedding
for my son and my daughter-in-law.
Okay, mother-in-law Bala. As you say.
We went through lots of hardships and tests.
We did not give up.
And we were blessed with a miracle.
And our love is still as the same as the first day.
That's right.
Those who have a great
love, will also have great tests.
Well...
...this hardship is what fuels the fire of love.
They will go through tests,
and they will be rewarded for it.
I hope so, Osman.
They are together now.
Hopefully they will be safe.
As long as I am here, no one can harm our children.
I know Osman.
But I can't stop being afraid.
Yakup Bey won't stay put.
There is a great scheme against Alaeddin.
They did it before, too, but they failed.
We defeated them.
They will lose again.
I hope so.
We showed our power to the infidels.
We paved our path.
Now we will show them our power
without spilling the blood of our brothers.
Ahmet!
My son!
My lion
My child!
You will feel cold under the ground!
My child.
I swear those who killed you will be destroyed.
The flames of hell will
rise and fall into their tent!
My child.
My child!
The herd of sheep got precautions.
Let my children sharpen their fangs.
We will tear the flesh from their bones.
Your land will be destroyed by my children.
Take one last look.
You are brave.
But you can't just hunt by showing them teeth.
I trained all those alps.
I guess things will be easier.
My sons are hungry for blood.
When the people are gone...
....we'll attack.
You go to the tent.
I will go to Ahmet's grave.
Alps.
Don't come with me.
My Bey. Ibrahim Bey didn't want him buried in Kayi.
He's buried in Cukurvadi.
Alright. Come on son.
Okay my Bey.
Bala Hatun.
Are Alaeddin and Gonca okay?
They’re okay my girl.
They’re married.
But they'll hide it until the judge comes.
Thankfully. I'm so happy.
That's right.
At least their tale ended happily
Well...
Bala Hatun.
I know it's not the place...
...but the ship...
When will it come?
I want to go to Constantinople.
I know my girl.
I understand
But it's not the time. There's chaos.
The roads are dangerous.
We can secure the roads.
And send Alps beforehand.
We must save Alaeddin first.
We must all deal with it.
B We can't secure Holofira.
There are baciyans if no Alps.
And...
...I'll help.
I owe Holofira a lot.
I want her to get her wish.
Elcim Hatun.
-Orhan.
Orhan.
My girl.
It's not the time to pay her.
I know you're kind.
But I won't put any of you in danger.
Holofira.
You should stay longer.
You're dealing with so much.
I don't wish to cause trouble.
I'll do as you wish.
Thanks.
Let's go then.
Come on.
Come on Elcim Hatun.
I'm in pain.
There's a fire in my heart that won't be put out.
My Ahmet.
You placed my heart into the
lands of the enemy Ibrahim.
It's time will come, wife.
This soil that is embracing our son...
..will soon be ours.
Keep your promise.
Take these lands.
Ibrahim...
...they set my heart aflame.
Rip their hearts out.
Rip it out...
I will keep my promise.
I'm going to do something so much worse...
...than death to the one who took ours son's...
...life and set our hearts aflame.
Ibrahim Bey.
It's time.
Be prepared.
Everyone went away. It's time to hunt.
We’re going to save the beys and kill the alps.
The grave will overflow with the blood of the alps.
Are you ready for the slaughter Boran?
Always.
Just take care of your own men.
We'll see.
If you hesitate...
...my sword will appear right on your neck.
We fulfilled our duty.
May Allah give his sins.
Ameen.
Let's go beys.
Come on.
Who do we have here?
An Osman Bey who is running to his death.
Be ready.
Captivity ends here.
Come on.
My bey.
I swear, I won't let...
...brothers kill brothers in these lands!
Visit turkision.com for more!